Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1994 March-1994 April; DVD (Disc 86)
    - Thanks, Dick Nourse, 1994 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Homeless check off, 1994 March 2 (Video 2)
    - To tax or not to tax, 1994 March 3 (Video 3)
    - Healthy heart month, 1994 March 4 (Video 4)
    - Bargains in education, 1994 March 7 (Video 5)
    - Reduce freeway solutions, 1994 March 8 (Video 6)
    - B.S.T. is no danger, 1994 March 9 (Video 7)
    - Language of choice, 1994 March 10 (Video 8)
    - Death of cities, 1994 March 11 (Video 9)
    - Honors to officers, 1994 March 14 (Video 10)
    - Middle school week, 1994 March 15 (Video 11)
    - Preserving the foothills, 1994 March 16 (Video 12)
    - Mideast caldron boils, 1994 March 17 (Video 13)
    - Utah's bright future, 1994 March 18 (Video 14)
    - Zero tolerance policy, 1994 March 21 (Video 15)
    - California gets tough, 1994 March 22 (Video 16)
    - Fox in the henhouse, 1994 March 23 (Video 17)
    - Doctor assisted suicide, 1994 March 24 (Video 18)
    - Abuse of power, 1994 March 25 (Video 19)
    - Yellow journalism again, 1994 March 28 (Video 20)
    - Postal rate increase, 1994 March 29 (Video 21)
    - Guns and reality, 1994 March 30 (Video 22)
    - Ethics and honesty, 1994 March 31 (Video 23)
    - World not in danger, 1994 April 1 (Video 24)
    - Fame is fleeting, 1994 April 4 (Video 25)
    - High school detectors, 1994 April 5 (Video 26)
    - Glen Canyon power, 1994 April 6 (Video 27)
    - Congress falls short, 1994 April 7 (Video 28)
    - Violence and indecency, 1994 April 8 (Video 29)
    - Welcome to the buzz, 1994 April 11 (Video 30)
    - Crime and prisons, 1994 April 12 (Video 31)
    - Driving made difficult, 1994 April 13 (Video 32)
    - Drugs for sale, 1994 April 14 (Video 33)
    - Children and aggression, 1994 April 15 (Video 34)
    - Taxes and elections, 1994 April 18 (Video 35)
    - Justice Blackmun retires, 1994 April 19 (Video 36)
    - Volunteers make the difference, 1994 April 20 (Video 37)
    - Organ donors needed, 1994 April 21 (Video 38)
    - Where taxes go, 1994 April 22 (Video 39)
    - Salt Palace overbid, 1994 April 25 (Video 40)
    - Congress arrives late, 1994 April 26 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view: Blake Hawkes, re guns, 1994 April 27 (Video 42)
    - Bosnia tragedy continues, 1994 April 28 (Video 43)
    - Plant a tree, 1994 April 29 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1994 May-1994 June; DVD (Disc 87)
    - Law Day, 1994 May 2 (Video 1)
    - Success by six, 1994 May 3 (Video 2)
    - WAC conference expands, 1994 May 4 (Video 3)
    - Clothing codes fail, 1994 May 5 (Video 4)
    - President is wrong, 1994 May 6 (Video 5)
    - Human rights conference, 1994 May 9 (Video 6)
    - Another point of view: Doug Christiansen, re guns, 1994 May 10 (Video 7)
    - South Africa triumph, 1994 May 11 (Video 8)
    - Check the facts, 1994 May 12 (Video 9)
    - Spring in Utah, 1994 May 13 (Video 10)
    - Social security sound, 1994 May 16 (Video 11)
    - Mayor has courage, 1994 May 17 (Video 12)
    - Hogle zoo problems, 1994 May 18 (Video 13)
    - Work, not exercise, 1994 May 19 (Video 14)
    - Park entrance fees, 1994 May 20 (Video 15)
    - Higher education salaries, 1994 May 23 (Video 16)
    - Illogical stock market, 1994 May 24 (Video 17)
    - Changing the future, 1994 May 25 (Video 18)
    - Welcome new technology, 1994 May 26 (Video 19)
    - Provo Canyon highway, 1994 May 27 (Video 20)
    - Embargo for Haiti, 1994 May 30 (Video 21)
    - Ezra Taft Benson, 1994 May 31 (Video 22)
    - Utah vacation time, 1994 June 1 (Video 23)
    - UDOT light controls, 1994 June 2 (Video 24)
    - Hill field rumors, 1994 June 3 (Video 25)
    - D-day plus fifty, 1994 June 6 (Video 26)
    - Lawmakers and meetings, 1994 June 7 (Video 27)
    - Child welfare reform, 1994 June 8 (Video 28)
    - What's in a name?, 1994 June 9 (Video 29)
    - Conference of the states, 1994 June 10 (Video 30)
    - Control North Korea, 1994 June 13 (Video 31)
    - Commandments should stay, 1994 June 14 (Video 32)
    - Rosty on trial, 1994 June 15 (Video 33)
    - Bad moo breath, 1994 June 16 (Video 34)
    - Free speech penalty, 1994 June 17 (Video 35)
    - Bachauer piano month, 1994 June 20 (Video 36)
    - To a great neighbor, 1994 June 21 (Video 37)
    - G.I. bill at fifty, 1994 June 22 (Video 38)
    - Holding up progress, 1994 June 23 (Video 39)
    - Police awards lunch, 1994 June 24 (Video 40)
    - Fall of a hero, 1994 June 27 (Video 41)
    - Holladay property taxes, 1994 June 28 (Video 42)
    - China's trade status, 1994 June 29 (Video 43)
    - Seperate is not equal, 1994 June 30 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1994 July-1994 August; DVD (Disc 88)
    - Fixing Latin America, 1994 July 1 (Video 1)
    - U.S. autos revive, 1994 July 4 (Video 2)
    - Role of the court, 1994 July 5 (Video 3)
    - Change is for certain, 1994 July 6 (Video 4)
    - Immunize children now, 1994 July 7 (Video 5)
    - Creators and discoveries, 1994 July 8 (Video 6)
    - Yasser Arafat returns, 1994 July 11 (Video 7)
    - Growth in St. George, 1994 July 12 (Video 8)
    - Reform outlook dim, 1994 July 13 (Video 9)
    - Golf and environment, 1994 July 14 (Video 10)
    - Medicine and change, 1994 July 15 (Video 11)
    - When bodies collide, 1994 July 18 (Video 12)
    - Glendale youth center, 1994 July 19 (Video 13)
    - Man on the moon, 1994 July 20 (Video 14)
    - Guam celebrates liberation, 1994 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Days of '47, 1994 July 22 (Video 16)
    - Yesterday and tomorrow, 1994 July 25 (Video 17)
    - Goldbricks at the mall, 1994 July 26 (Video 18)
    - Utah state fairpark, 1994 July 27 (Video 19)
    - Protect Sugarhouse Park, 1994 July 28 (Video 20)
    - Good deeds galore, 1994 July 29 (Video 21)
    - Rwanda adds sorrow, 1994 August 1 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view: Vernon Goldsmith, re environment, 1994 August 2 (Video 23)
    - Baseball strike out, 1994 August 3 (Video 24)
    - Cameras in court, 1994 August 4 (Video 25)
    - Universal coverage exists, 1994 August 5 (Video 26)
    - Campaign reform needed, 1994 August 8 (Video 27)
    - Another point of view: David Humes, re change, 1994 August 9 (Video 28)
    - Limiting voter freedom, 1994 August 10 (Video 29)
    - This woman's navy, 1994 August 11 (Video 30)
    - Tax return privacy, 1994 August 12 (Video 31)
    - Court torpedoes efficiency, 1994 August 15 (Video 32)
    - Central Utah project, 1994 August 16 (Video 33)
    - P.S.C. looks ahead, 1994 August 17 (Video 34)
    - Deficit on the mend, 1994 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Japan's safe streets, 1994 August 19 (Video 36)
    - Action on block 49, 1994 August 22 (Video 37)
    - Politics and crime, 1994 August 23 (Video 38)
    - Garden visitors center, 1994 August 24 (Video 39)
    - Road to Budapest, 1994 August 25 (Video 40)
    - Welfare reform smoke, 1994 August 26 (Video 41)
    - Cuba policy change, 1994 August 29 (Video 42)
    - Troubled postal service, 1994 August 30 (Video 43)
    - Preschool crime prevention, 1994 August 31 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1994 September-1994 October; DVD (Disc 89)
    - Dress down day, 1994 September 1 (Video 1)
    - Football season arrives, 1994 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Labor Day, 1994 September 5 (Video 3)
    - Congress goes home, 1994 September 6 (Video 4)
    - Blurring the lines, 1994 September 7 (Video 5)
    - River bend golf, 1994 September 8 (Video 6)
    - Health care changes, 1994 September 9 (Video 7)
    - Goodbye, Salt Palace, 1994 September 12 (Video 8)
    - Deer on the road, 1994 September 13 (Video 9)
    - Look inside courts, 1994 September 14 (Video 10)
    - Arts and education, 1994 September 15 (Video 11)
    - Utah is booming, 1994 September 16 (Video 12)
    - Plant a tree, 1994 September 19 (Video 13)
    - Study of aging, 1994 September 20 (Video 14)
    - Depression era wisdom, 1994 September 21 (Video 15)
    - Eating and guilt, 1994 September 22 (Video 16)
    - America's moral revival, 1994 September 23 (Video 17)
    - Success in Haiti, 1994 September 26 (Video 18)
    - Road to Bountiful, 1994 September 27 (Video 19)
    - News references mistaken, 1994 September 28 (Video 20)
    - World invovlement necessary, 1994 September 29 (Video 21)
    - Gambling on television, 1994 September 30 (Video 22)
    - Double murder questions, 1994 October 3 (Video 23)
    - Ignorance about Cuba, 1994 October 4 (Video 24)
    - Crime Prevention Month, 1994 October 5 (Video 25)
    - Praise for diversity, 1994 October 6 (Video 26)
    - Reality versus fantasy, 1994 October 7 (Video 27)
    - Mark Eaton retires, 1994 October 10 (Video 28)
    - Punish tree spikers, 1994 October 11 (Video 29)
    - "Contract with America", 1994 October 12 (Video 30)
    - Billy's best day, 1994 October 13 (Video 31)
    - New money ahead, 1994 October 14 (Video 32)
    - Time for flu shots, 1994 October 17 (Video 33)
    - Term limits vote, 1994 October 18 (Video 34)
    - Jordan River parkway, 1994 October 19 (Video 35)
    - Civil discourse disappears, 1994 October 20 (Video 36)
    - Talk radio reality, 1994 October 21 (Video 37)
    - Utah ballot decisions, 1994 October 24 (Video 38)
    - Typical of region, 1994 October 25 (Video 39)
    - Schools or prisons, 1994 October 26 (Video 40)
    - Help for Alzheimer's, 1994 October 27 (Video 41)
    - Life without telephones, 1994 October 28 (Video 42)
    - Dale Harding resigns, 1994 October 31 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1994 November-1994 December; DVD (Disc 90)
    - Another point of view: David Bresnahan, re guns (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 1 (Video 1)
    - Race and I.Q. (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 2 (Video 2)
    - Another point of view: Jan Graham, re proposition 1 (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 3 (Video 3)
    - Utah kids count (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 4 (Video 4)
    - Your vote counts (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 7 (Video 5)
    - Forget McDonnell Douglas deal (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 8 (Video 6)
    - Enough negative campaigns (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 9 (Video 7)
    - Top-flight corporate citizens (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 10 (Video 8)
    - Veterans Day (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 11 (Video 9)
    - Winners and losers (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 14 (Video 10)
    - Approve GATT accord (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 15 (Video 11)
    - Solving traffic problems (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 16 (Video 12)
    - Sad young cynics (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 17 (Video 13)
    - Most remarkable decade (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 18 (Video 14)
    - Revolution in Congress (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 21 (Video 15)
    - Problems in California (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 22 (Video 16)
    - Thanksgiving (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 23 (Video 17)
    - Feeding the hungry (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 24 (Video 18)
    - Airplane flyover tax (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 25 (Video 19)
    - Safe at home (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 28 (Video 20)
    - Denver airport woes (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 29 (Video 21)
    - Hollywood misses mark (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 November 30 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view: Thomas Breitling, re GATT agreement (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 1 (Video 23)
    - Long, cold winter (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 2 (Video 24)
    - Hanukkah (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 5 (Video 25)
    - Another point of view: David Adams re McDonnell Douglas, 1994 December 6 (Video 26)
    - Quarters for Christmas (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 7 (Video 27)
    - Another point of view: Claire Geddes, re GATT agreement (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 8 (Video 28)
    - Good times blues (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 9 (Video 29)
    - Season to be jolly (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 12 (Video 30)
    - Banks and risk (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 13 (Video 31)
    - What state surplus? (Archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 14 (Video 32)
    - Property tax repair (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 15 (Video 33)
    - What about Bosnia? (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 16 (Video 34)
    - Orange County bankrupt (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 19 (Video 35)
    - Another point of view: Brent Overson, re flyover tax (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 20 (Video 36)
    - Genetics and medicine (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 21 (Video 37)
    - County jail activity (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 22 (Video 38)
    - Merry Christmas (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 23 (Video 39)
    - America's political unrest (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 26 (Video 40)
    - Welfare time limits (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 27 (Video 41)
    - White House shooting (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 28 (Video 42)
    - Faces of Utah (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 29 (Video 43)
    - Happy New Year (archive tape for November-December 1994 is missing), 1994 December 30 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1995 January-1995 February; DVD (Disc 91)
    - Changes at KSL-TV, 1995 January 2 (Video 1)
    - Promise of 1995, 1995 January 3 (Video 2)
    - Governor's budget plan, 1995 January 4 (Video 3)
    - Outlaw impact fees, 1995 January 5 (Video 4)
    - Down the highway, 1995 January 6 (Video 5)
    - Keep public broadcasting, 1995 January 9 (Video 6)
    - Retain trash pickup, 1995 January 10 (Video 7)
    - Funding for the arts, 1995 January 11 (Video 8)
    - Checkoff for homeless, 1995 January 12 (Video 9)
    - Volunteers in Utah, 1995 January 13 (Video 10)
    - Human Rights Day, 1995 January 16 (Video 11)
    - Baseball and hockey, 1995 January 17 (Video 12)
    - Violence and schools, 1995 January 18 (Video 13)
    - Rosy economic forecast, 1995 January 19 (Video 14)
    - Balance the budget, 1995 January 20 (Video 15)
    - Changes in Congress, 1995 January 23 (Video 16)
    - Values in school, 1995 January 24 (Video 17)
    - Nuts over tax cuts, 1995 January 25 (Video 18)
    - Welcome, Bishop Niederauer, 1995 January 26 (Video 19)
    - Unfunded mandate relief, 1995 January 27 (Video 20)
    - Countdown to one hundred, 1995 January 30 (Video 21)
    - Olympic bid dangers, 1995 January 31 (Video 22)
    - Surprise tax proposal, 1995 February 1 (Video 23)
    - Change phone regulation, 1995 February 2 (Video 24)
    - The O.J. spectacle, 1995 February 3 (Video 25)
    - Another KSL radiothon, 1995 February 6 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view: Kenneth Bullock, re impact fees, 1995 February 7 (Video 27)
    - Health education centers, 1995 February 8 (Video 28)
    - State art treasures, 1995 February 9 (Video 29)
    - Why not Mexico?, 1995 February 10 (Video 30)
    - Libraries and art, 1995 February 13 (Video 31)
    - Black History Month, 1995 February 14 (Video 32)
    - Family services upgrade, 1995 February 15 (Video 33)
    - Semester or quarters, 1995 February 16 (Video 34)
    - Wolves are back, 1995 February 17 (Video 35)
    - Fathers deserve blame, 1995 February 20 (Video 36)
    - Hands off sports, 1995 February 21 (Video 37)
    - Water rights primer, 1995 February 22 (Video 38)
    - Soft on crime, 1995 February 23 (Video 39)
    - Federal reserve restraint, 1995 February 24 (Video 40)
    - Thanks, KSL listeners, 1995 February 27 (Video 41)
    - Let's eat out, 1995 February 28 (Video 42)
  - KSL editorials, 1995 March-1995 April; DVD (Disc 92)
    - Distrust turned inward (not recorded for archive), 1995 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Legislature goes home, 1995 March 2 (Video 2)
    - Howard W. Hunter, 1995 March 3 (Video 3)
    - Middle school month, 1995 March 6 (Video 4)
    - Danger of projections, 1995 March 7 (Video 5)
    - Alibi Ike syndrome, 1995 March 8 (Video 6)
    - In search of heroes, 1995 March 9 (Video 7)
    - Test ban treaty, 1995 March 10 (Video 8)
    - Veto gun bill, 1995 March 13 (Video 9)
    - Gordon B. Hinckley, 1995 March 14 (Video 10)
    - Year of the family, 1995 March 15 (Video 11)
    - Balanced budget action, 1995 March 16 (Video 12)
    - Clinton's foreign policy, 1995 March 17 (Video 13)
    - Welcome, micron technology, 1995 March 20 (Video 14)
    - Another point of view: David Bresnahan, violence in security, 1995 March 21 (Video 15)
    - Celebration of the century, 1995 March 22 (Video 16)
    - COLAs should go, 1995 March 23 (Video 17)
    - Food danger realities, 1995 March 24 (Video 18)
    - Super sports year, 1995 March 27 (Video 19)
    - Another point of view: Mark Kleinfeld, re family services, 1995 March 28 (Video 20)
    - Conference against violence, 1995 March 29 (Video 21)
    - Politics and sports, 1995 March 30 (Video 22)
    - Power of one, 1995 March 31 (Video 23)
    - Minimum mandatory sentences, 1995 April 3 (Video 24)
    - Another point of view: Michael Megeath, re guns, 1995 April 4 (Video 25)
    - Tuacahn at St. George, 1995 April 5 (Video 26)
    - City skyline changing, 1995 April 6 (Video 27)
    - New downtown park, 1995 April 7 (Video 28)
    - Five thousand editorials, 1995 April 10 (Video 29)
    - Another point of view: Ted Stewart, re Colorado River water, 1995 April 11 (Video 30)
    - Wilderness and civility, 1995 April 12 (Video 31)
    - Watch for rumors, 1995 April 13 (Video 32)
    - State park expands, 1995 April 14 (Video 33)
    - Freeway watch success, 1995 April 17 (Video 34)
    - Affirmative action politics, 1995 April 18 (Video 35)
    - Organ donors needed, 1995 April 19 (Video 36)
    - Don't abandon arttix, 1995 April 20 (Video 37)
    - Children and pigs, 1995 April 21 (Video 38)
    - It's secretaries week, 1995 April 24 (Video 39)
    - Another point of view: Claire Geddes, re NAFTA, 1995 April 25 (Video 40)
    - Robert McNamara talks, 1995 April 26 (Video 41)
    - Teaching good habits, 1995 April 27 (Video 42)
    - Arbor Day, 1995 April 28 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1995 May-1995 June; DVD (Disc 93)
    - Vital role of law, 1995 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Tragedy in Oklahoma, 1995 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Arts and children, 1995 May 3 (Video 3)
    - Budget debate smokescreen, 1995 May 4 (Video 4)
    - Traffic computer ahead, 1995 May 5 (Video 5)
    - Baby Richard Case, 1995 May 8 (Video 6)
    - About militia groups, 1995 May 9 (Video 7)
    - Hooray for the Jazz, 1995 May 10 (Video 8)
    - Approve new jail, 1995 May 11 (Video 9)
    - Preserve American values, 1995 May 12 (Video 10)
    - City budget on track, 1995 May 15 (Video 11)
    - East high towers, 1995 May 16 (Video 12)
    - Immunize the children, 1995 May 17 (Video 13)
    - Caring about others, 1995 May 18 (Video 14)
    - Justice system works, 1995 May 19 (Video 15)
    - Great wilderness debate, 1995 May 22 (Video 16)
    - Apples and oranges, 1995 May 23 (Video 17)
    - Baseball strikes out, 1995 May 24 (Video 18)
    - Journey into cyberspace, 1995 May 25 (Video 19)
    - Top ten medical advances, 1995 May 26 (Video 20)
    - Term limits outlawed, 1995 May 29 (Video 21)
    - Why so much despair?, 1995 May 30 (Video 22)
    - Glorious Utah spring, 1995 May 31 (Video 23)
    - Graduation energy boost, 1995 June 1 (Video 24)
    - Smoking and hypocrisy, 1995 June 2 (Video 25)
    - Balanced budget possibility, 1995 June 5 (Video 26)
    - Serbs earn outrage, 1995 June 6 (Video 27)
    - Shoplifting and you, 1995 June 7 (Video 28)
    - Ebola and reason, 1995 June 8 (Video 29)
    - Common sense and law, 1995 June 9 (Video 30)
    - Olympics party fun, 1995 June 12 (Video 31)
    - Summer time danger, 1995 June 13 (Video 32)
    - Learn about medicare, 1995 June 14 (Video 33)
    - Festival time in Utah, 1995 June 15 (Video 34)
    - Thanks, Utah volunteers, 1995 June 16 (Video 35)
    - Brooks arcade nonsense, 1995 June 19 (Video 36)
    - Thanks, Charles Dick, 1995 June 20 (Video 37)
    - Endangered species caution, 1995 June 21 (Video 38)
    - History predicts future, 1995 June 22 (Video 39)
    - Boomers turn to religion, 1995 June 23 (Video 40)
    - Olympics benefits apparent, 1995 June 26 (Video 41)
    - Thanks, olympic boosters, 1995 June 27 (Video 42)
    - Hungary offers example, 1995 June 28 (Video 43)
    - Power of the olympics, 1995 June 29 (Video 44)
    - Stick to facts, 1995 June 30 (Video 45)
  - KSL editorials, 1995 July-1995 August; DVD (Disc 94)
    - Look at all lobbies, 1995 July 3 (Video 1)
    - Keep sense of humor, 1995 July 4 (Video 2)
    - Clean up the freeway, 1995 July 5 (Video 3)
    - On being good citizens, 1995 July 6 (Video 4)
    - Nation of slobs, 1995 July 7 (Video 5)
    - Stop neighborhood crime, 1995 July 10 (Video 6)
    - Managed health care, 1995 July 11 (Video 7)
    - New ideas in education, 1995 July 12 (Video 8)
    - Clicker control contest, 1995 July 13 (Video 9)
    - Values and lifestyle, 1995 July 14 (Video 10)
    - Micron breaks ground, 1995 July 17 (Video 11)
    - Highway cleanup project, 1995 July 18 (Video 12)
    - Sons of Ramesses, 1995 July 19 (Video 13)
    - Traffic will increase, 1995 July 20 (Video 14)
    - Nuclear waste transport, 1995 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Days of '47, 1995 July 24 (Video 16)
    - Growth summit set, 1995 July 25 (Video 17)
    - SBA deserves support, 1995 July 26 (Video 18)
    - Jobs and technology, 1995 July 27 (Video 19)
    - Register your car, 1995 July 28 (Video 20)
    - George Romney, 1995 July 31 (Video 21)
    - Dilemma in Bosnia, 1995 August 1 (Video 22)
    - Hogle zoo support, 1995 August 2 (Video 23)
    - Roses and sagebrush, 1995 August 3 (Video 24)
    - Dropping the bomb, 1995 August 4 (Video 25)
    - Miles Goodyear remembered, 1995 August 7 (Video 26)
    - Distrust is epidemic, 1995 August 8 (Video 27)
    - Fillmore makes history, 1995 August 9 (Video 28)
    - Preserve farm land, 1995 August 10 (Video 29)
    - Nation of math illiterates, 1995 August 11 (Video 30)
    - V-J day plus 50, 1995 August 14 (Video 31)
    - Look forward, Congress, 1995 August 15 (Video 32)
    - Property tax notices, 1995 August 16 (Video 33)
    - Arts education needed, 1995 August 17 (Video 34)
    - Butterflies are free, 1995 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Tobacco and children, 1995 August 21 (Video 36)
    - Protect University Hospital, 1995 August 22 (Video 37)
    - Credo for happiness, 1995 August 23 (Video 38)
    - Using yesterday's solutions, 1995 August 24 (Video 39)
    - Medicare under attack, 1995 August 25 (Video 40)